Guide to the The Charles D. Field Collection of Ernest Hemingway
Department of Special Collections
The Charles D. Field Collection of Ernest Hemingway
Special Collections M0440
Hemingway, Ernest, 1899-1961.
1.25 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Charles D. Field, 1985 and 1986.
Procedures for Requesting Permission to Publish Portions of the Works of Ernest Hemingway
I. Unpublished Works and Works Posthumously Published in Periodicals or Anthologies:
U.S. Publication
Requests for rights to publish unpublished letters, and to republish letters posthumously published in journals or anthologies, in the U.S. in all markets must conform to the requirements listed under Form of Request below, and should be directed to:
The Ernest Hemingway Foundation
c/o Prof. Allen Josephs, President
University of West Florida
11000 University Parkway
Pensacola, Florida 32514-5751
Phone: 904/474-2925
Fax: 904/474-2935
with a complete copy to Stults & Balber, P.C., 1370 Avenue of the Americas, 30th Floor, New York, New York 10019, Attn.: Tracy Green Landauer, Esq.
Requests for rights to publish other unpublished materials, and materials posthumously published in journals or anthologies, in the U.S. are jointly controlled by the Foundation and the sons of Ernest Hemingway and should be directed to both:
The Ernest Hemingway Foundation
c/o Prof. Allen Josephs, President
University of West Florida
11000 University Parkway
Pensacola, Florida 32514-5751
Phone: 904/474-2925
Fax: 904/474/2935
and
John and Patrick Hemingway
c/o Michael Katakis
13550 Skunk Creek Road
Bozeman, Montana 59715
Phone: 406/686-4980
Fax: 406/686-4496
with a complete copy to Stults & Balber, P.C., 1370 Avenue of the Americas, 30th Floor, New York, New York 10019, Attn.: Tracy Green Landauer, Esq.
Outside the U.S.
Requests to publish or republish the above material outside the U.S. should be directed to:
John and Patrick Hemingway
c/o Michael Katakis
13550 Skunk Creek Road
Bozeman, Montana 59715
Phone: 406/686-4980
Fax: 406/686-4496
Permissions Policy:
Permission to publish material controlled by the Ernest Hemingway Foundation will be granted in accordance with the following guidelines:
-Single quotations should not exceed 150 words.*
-The aggregate quotations from a single work should not exceed 10% of that work.*
-Payment of the fee must be received in advance.
-The publication must include notice of copyright for the quoted material as follows: © [year of publication] The Ernest Hemingway Foundation.
-The author must provide two copies of the final publication, one to the President of the Foundation and one to Stults & Balber, P.C. at the addresses shown above.
* Exceptions to the amount of material permitted to be quoted will be made only if the author demonstrates to the satisfaction of the Foundation that he or she cannot adequately present or substantiate a critical argument without occasional longer quotations.
Fees: Fees will be determined on the basis of (1) whether the request is for a commercial or scholarly publication, and (2) the amount and nature of the material to be quoted.
-Commercial publications (generally print runs of more than 5,000 copies, coupled with royalties): Authors must reach agreement with the Foundation as to an appropriate fee, which may in some instances include a division of royalties. The usual rate is $100 to $500 per letter for quotations that meet the above guidelines.
-Scholarly publications (generally articles in scholarly journals or critical collections, and books of literary history, criticism or biography with anticipated sales of less than 5,000 copies): Authors will typically be charged a fee of $100 to $500 per letter for quotations that meet the above guidelines.
Reductions in these fees may be granted at the sole discretion of the Foundation upon demonstration that the author's total compensation from the publication would be disproportionately small relative to the cost of permission. Generally, the Foundation's fee will not exceed 50% of the author's total compensation.
Form of request:
Requests made to The Ernest Hemingway Foundation (and copies sent to Stults & Balber, P.C.) must include:
-two (2) copies of the quotation(s) for which permission is requested
-full identification of the passage(s) in the manuscript, collection or anthology
-the word count for each quotation
-the percentage that the quotation constitutes of the work in which it originally appears
-the abstract of the article or chapter outline of the book in which the quotation is intended to be published; and
-the name and address of the intended publisher, together with full information as to the scope of rights requested and the (a) circulation (in the case of journal publication), or (b) size and nature of the anticipated print run.
[UNK] [UNK]
II. Published Volumes:
U.S. and Canada
Requests concerning U.S. and Canadian publication of excerpts from Ernest Hemingway: Selected Letters 1917-1961 and The Nick Adams Stories, or from Across the River and into the Trees, By-Line Ernest Hemingway, Complete Short Stories of Ernest Hemingway, Dangerous Summer, Dateline: Toronto, Death in the Afternoon, A Farewell to Arms, The Fifth Column and Four Stories of the Spanish Civil War, For Whom the Bell Tolls, Garden of Eden, Green Hills of Africa, The Hemingway Reader, In Our Time, Islands in the Stream, Men Without Women, A Moveable Feast, The Old Man and the Sea, Short Stories of Ernest Hemingway, The Snows of Kilimanjaro and Other Stories, The Sun Also Rises, To Have and Have Not. Torrents of Spring, and Winner Take Nothing should be directed to:
Simon & Schuster
Consumer Permissions
1633 Broadway
New York, New York 10019
Attn.: Ms. Lydia Zelaya
Phone: 212/654-7503
Fax: 212/654-4782
Requests concerning U.S. and Canadian publication of excerpts from 88 Poems should be directed to:
Permissions Department
Harcourt Brace & Company
Orlando, Florida 32887
Phone: 407/345-2000
Fax: 407/352-8860
Outside the U.S. and Canada
Requests for the rights to publish excerpts from such volumes outside the U.S. and Canada should be directed to:
John and Patrick Hemingway
c/o Mr. Michael Katakis
13550 Skunk Creek Road
Bozeman, Montana 59715
Phone: 406/686/4980
Fax: 406/686/4496
M440
Hemingway
Container List
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 35a (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 42 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 97 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 110 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 129 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 148 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 154 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Stories, articles by Ernest Hemingway, item 206 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ephemera, reprints of letters, item 209 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ephemera, reprints of letters, item 210 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ephemera, reprints of letters, item 211 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ephemera, reprints of letters, item 212 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ephemera, reprints of letters, item 213 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ephemera, reprints of letters, item 214 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Ephemera, reprints of letters, item 215 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 230 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 232 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 241 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 286 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 292 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 293 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 295 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 297-300 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 304 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 305 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 308 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 310 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 312 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 314-315 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 316 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 317 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 318 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 320 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 321 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 322 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 323 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 324 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 325 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 326 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 327 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 328 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 329-330 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 331 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 332 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 333 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 334 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 335 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 336 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 337 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 338 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 339-340 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 341 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 342-343 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Articles, newsclippings, pamphlets about Ernest Hemingway, item 344 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Lecture series program, 5 postcards of Hemingway residence, item 345 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Lecture series program, item 346-350 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Correspondence
  - Aitken, 17 Mar. 1936,item 351 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Attwood, 10 July 1956,item 352 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 353 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 354 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 355 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 356 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 357 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 358 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 359 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 360 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 361 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 362 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 363 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 364 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 365 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 366 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 367 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 368 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 369 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 370 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 371 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 372 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 373 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 374 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 375 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 376 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 377 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 378 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 379 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 380 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 381 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 382 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Baker, 17 Feb. 1951-26 Jan. 1961,item 383 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Black Sun Press, Aug.-Oct. 1931,item 384-385 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Spruille Braden, 6 Oct.-2 Dec. 1943,item 386-388 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bromfield, 8 Mar. 1926,item 389 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Calmer, 28 May 1934-22 July 1936,item 390-394 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chase, 1 Apr. 1946,item 395 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Davis, [ca. 1942],item 396 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Demperwolf, 24 June 1927,item 397 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Drake, 21 Nov. [1929],item 398 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Goldstein, 16 Mar. [1921],item 399 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Hapgood, Dec. 1922-12 Jan. 1925,item 400-402 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Hayward, [ca. May 1956],item 403 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - C. Hemingway, 19 Oct. 1908,item 404 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - L. Hemingway, 20 Mar. 1955-14 Sept. 1959,item 405 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - L. Hemingway, 20 Mar. 1955-14 Sept. 1959,item 406 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - L. Hemingway, 20 Mar. 1955-14 Sept. 1959,item 407 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - L. Hemingway, 20 Mar. 1955-14 Sept. 1959,item 408 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - P. and G. Hemingway, 14 Dec. 1948,item 409 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Hogan, 19 Dec. 1946,item 410 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Hopkins, 6 Dec. 1935-31 Mar. 1936,item 411-416 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 417 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 418 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 419 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 420 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 421 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 422 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 423 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 424 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 425 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Horwitz, 13 Aug. 1948-20 Nov. 1951,item 426 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Jenkins, 20 Dec. 1919-8 Jan. 1922,item 427 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Jenkins, 20 Dec. 1919-8 Jan. 1922,item 428 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Jenkins, 20 Dec. 1919-8 Jan. 1922,item 429 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Matthews, 24 Aug. 1960-13 Sept. 1960,item 430 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Matthews, 24 Aug. 1960-13 Sept. 1960,item 431 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - de Pereda, 13 Apr. 1934-30 Oct. 1947,item 432 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - de Pereda, 13 Apr. 1934-30 Oct. 1947,item 433 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - de Pereda, 13 Apr. 1934-30 Oct. 1947,item 434 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - de Pereda, 13 Apr. 1934-30 Oct. 1947,item 435 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - de Pereda, 13 Apr. 1934-30 Oct. 1947,item 436 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Perry, [ca. 7 Feb. 1933],item 437 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Pfeiffer, 1 Jan. [ca. 1934],item 438 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Poore, 8 Aug. 1949,item 439 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Prentiss, 22 Feb. 1936,item 440 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 441 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 442 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 443 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 444 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 445 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 446 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 447 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 448 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 449 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Rakow, 29 June 1953-Dec. 1955,item 450 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Raymond, 8 May 1930,item 451 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Rudd, 13 Apr. 1956,item 452 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Ruhm, 10 Oct. 1950-6 Jan. 1951,item 453 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Ruhm, 10 Oct. 1950-6 Jan. 1951,item 454 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Ruhm, 21 June 1952-20 Apr. 1953,item 455 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Ruhm, 21 June 1952-20 Apr. 1953,item 456 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Ruhm, 21 June 1952-20 Apr. 1953,item 457 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Russell, 27 Oct. 1936,item 458 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Saltpeter, 16 Apr. 1936,item 459 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - M. Smith, [ca. 1948-1950],item 460 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - W. Smith, 4 Dec. 1919-3 Dec. 1925,item 461 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - W. Smith, 4 Dec. 1919-3 Dec. 1925,item 462 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - W. Smith, 4 Dec. 1919-3 Dec. 1925,item 463 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - W. Smith, 4 Dec. 1919-3 Dec. 1925,item 464 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Teague, 10 Aug. 1951,item 465 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Tibbits, 20 Jan. 1953,item 466 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Wheeler, 7 Mar. 1949,item 467 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Unknown, item 468 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Unknown, item 469 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Unknown, item 470 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Unknown, item 471 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Unknown, item 472 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Untitled poem, [ca. 1918-1920],item 473 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - The Sea Change, [ca. 1930],item 475 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - An Old Newspapersman Writes, [ca. 1934],item 476 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Remembering Shooting-Flying: A Key West Letter, [ca. 1934-1935],item 477 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sailfish off Mombasa: A Key West Letter, [ca. 1934-1935],item 478 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Life and Letters, a Manuscript Found in a Bottle, 15 Jan. 1935,item 479 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A New York Letter, [ca. 1935],item 480 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Tradesman's Return, [ca. 1935-1936],item 481 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Time Now, The Place Spain, [ca. 1938],item 482 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Next Outbreak of Peace, [ca. 1938-1939],item 483 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Last Will and Testament of Ernest M. Hemingway, 3 Dec. 1921,item 484 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Check to Ernest Hemingway for ¥'150 from Anthony B. Jenkinson, 6 Nov. 1941,item 485 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ernest Hemingway to [unknown], n.d.,item 486 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 487 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 488 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 489 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 490 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 491 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 492 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 493 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 494 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 495 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 496 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence relating to Ernest Hemingway, item 497 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Baker to Ernest Hemingway, photocopy (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Baker to Ernest Hemingway, photocopy (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Baker to Ernest Hemingway, photocopy (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Ernest Hemingway to Eric Edward Chink Dorman-Smith, Feb.-July 1950,addenda 86-055 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ernest Hemingway to Eric Edward Chink Dorman-Smith, Aug.-Dec. 1950, addenda 86-055 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ernest Hemingway to Eric Edward Chink Dorman-Smith, 1951, addenda 86-055 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ernest Hemingway to Eric Edward Chink Dorman-Smith, 1954, addenda 86-055 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Ernest Hemingway to Eric Edward Chink Dorman-Smith, 1955, addenda 86-055 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- OVERSIZE ITEMS
  - The Age Demanded, [ca. 1928],item 474 (Box OS1)
  - Black and white photograph of Ernest M. Hemingway, item 499
  - Photographs of Ernest Hemingway (11)